Periodicals Collection, 1784- (ongoing)
Sophia Smith Collection
Periodicals collection
1784- (ongoing)
MS 537
476 linear ft.
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
Periodicals Collection includes over 1,500 titles of current and historical, U.S. and international women's magazines, newsletters, and other serials. Holdings range from full-runs to single subscriptions for certain titles.
The SSC Periodicals Collection includes over 1,500 titles of current and historical, U.S. and international women's magazines, newsletters, and other serials dating from the 18th century to the present. Among these are Ladies' Companion (1840-1844), Woman's Journal (1870-1916), Lucifer: The Light Bearer (1897-1901), Eugenesia (Mexico, 1943-1945), Church Woman (1943-1949), Black Sash (South Africa, 1958-1972), and popular 20th century magazines such as Vogue (1950-2000) and Cosmopolitan (1953-92). Periodicals of the suffrage and birth control movements, and the mid-twentieth century women's liberation movement are well represented. The latter include titles such as Off Our Backs, Shrew, Rat and Velvet Fist. There are approximately fifty current subscriptions. Holdings range from full-runs to single issues for certain titles. Some titles are on microfilm.
Girl Zines form part of this collection and consist of 9 linear feet (18 boxes) of small, self-published magazines created primarily by young women and girls and share a strong feminist perspective. There is a separate finding aid for the Girl Zines.
The collection is open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection without any additional restrictions.
Some issues are on microfilm. Some fragile volumes have been photocopied for preservation purposes.
Regular additions are made to this collection and may not be reflected in this finding aid.
The periodicals in this collecion have been donated or purchased from a variety of sources over many years.
Birth control--Periodicals--History; Fashion--Periodicals--History; Feminism--Periodicals; Lesbianism--Periodicals; Women--International cooperation--Periodicals; Women--Suffrage--Periodicals; Women's periodicals, American--History; Women's rights--Periodicals--History; Young Women's Christian Association of the U.S.A.--Periodicals--History; Sophia Smith Collection
There are many periodicals located in other collections, such as the Margaret Sanger Papers and the Frances Casement Papers. Some are cross-referenced in the list below. See also the extensive list of serials in the YWCA Records, SERIES VI. Publications.
- Alphabetical by title
  - A
    - Advances in Planned Parenthood, 1967-81
    - Aegis - Magazine on Ending Violence Against Women (formerly Feminist Alliance Against Rape Newsletter)1974-87
    - Affiliates Bulletin (Planned Parenthood Federation of America)1952-1961, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Aframerican Woman's Journal1940-47
    - Africa's Modern Woman (Africa's Leading Illustrated Women's Magazine)1963-66
    - African Women (continuing as Women Today)1954-63
    - Ain't I a Woman?1970-74
    - AJWS (Asian Journal of Women's Studies)1998
    - The Alpha1884, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
    - Al-Raida1978-
    - Albatross1975
    - The Allegheny Feminist1979-81
    - The Alliance Journal (published by Alliance of Women for Equality
    - Maplewood, NJ)1971
    - Amazon1975-80
    - Amazon Quarterly, A Lesbian-Feminist Arts Journal1972-75
    - The Amazonian, 2000-2001
    - American Archivist1985-, [Staff Library]
    - American Girl1968-71
    - American Ladies Magazine1837
    - American Women's Club of Paris Bulletin, [see The Bulletin]
    - Amulet (and Ladies' Literary Cabinet)1827
    - The Annotated Guide to Women's Periodicals in the US and Canada1983-85
    - Anima1979
    - The Antiseptic1911, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Anti-Suffrage Review1909-12
    - Anti-Suffragist1908-12
    - Aphra1969-75
    - Archival Issues (formerly Midwestern Archivist)1992-97
    - Archivaria1991-
    - The Archivist1998-2003
    - Arise, 2002-2008
    - Artemis (later became Enterprising Women)1975-79
    - Arthur's Magazine (also known as Arthur's Home Magazine)1844-74
    - Asian Woman (formerly Asian Women's Institute Newsletter)1975-93
    - Asomante (San Juan, Puerto Rico)1956-58
    - The Association Monthly, (YWCA)1907-21
    - Atalanta (formerly ALFA)1975-86
    - Atlantic Monthly1864-65
    - AUF: Eine Frauenzeitschrift1981-88
    - Aurora1971-74
    - Awake and Move1971
    - Azalea: A Magazine by Third World Lesbians1978-80
  - B
    - Bad Attitude1984
    - Battle Acts1970-72
    - Behold the Woman1972
    - Berkeley Tribe1970-71
    - The Berkeley Women of Color1983-84
    - Between Our Selves: Women of Color Newspaper1985
    - The Bi Monthly: Newsletter of the Bisexual Center (San Francisco),1976-81
    - Big Apple Dyke News1981-82
    - Big Mama Rag1973-83
    - Biology and Human Affairs1947-1949, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Birth Control (Japan)1933-1952, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Birth Control Herald1925, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Birth Control News1934-40, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Birth Control News (London)1922-29, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Birth Control Review1917-40, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Birth Gazette (United Kingdom)1990
    - Bisexual Women's Liberation Newsletter (New York)1975
    - Black Belt Woman1975-76
    - Black Maria (Women Speak)1972-79
    - The Black Sash1956-82
    - Black Woman's Voice (National Council of Negro Women)1972-80
    - The Body Politic1994-97
    - Branching Out: Canadian Magazine for Women1974-77
    - Bread and Roses: A Midwestern Women's Journal of Issues and the Arts1979-80
    - Bread and Roses Newsletter1970-71
    - Breakthrough (later "NACW's Breakthrough") [National Association of Commissions for Women]1972-82
    - Bridges: A Journal for Jewish Feminists and Our Friends1990-95
    - Britannia1916
    - British Lady's Magazine1815
    - Broadsheet, the Feminist Magazine (New Zealand)1974-93
    - Broadside, "A Sampler" undated
    - Broadside, a Feminist Review1983
    - Broomstick, By, For, and About Women Over Forty1981-90
    - Brother: A Forum for Men Against Sexism1972-74
    - Brown Sister (Wellesley College)1977
    - The Bulletin (The American Women's Club of Paris, Inc.)1929-34
    - The Bulletin (Birth Control Federation of America, Inc.1940, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Bulletin: The National Council of Women in the U.S.1983
    - Bulletin of the International Socialist Women's Secretariat1955-59
    - Bulletin of Indian Women's Movement1937-41
  - C
    - CAAW (Council of Asian American Women)1978-80
    - CCWHP- Coordinating Committee on Women in the Historical Profession (formerly CGWH - Conference Group on Women's History)1970-93
    - Cadernos Condicao Feminina (Portugal)1982-84
    - Calgary Women's Newspaper1979
    - Calling All Women: News Letter of the Suffragette Fellowship1947-69
    - Calyx - A Northwest Feminist Review1976-2000
    - Cambridge Women's Liberation Newsletter1978-80
    - Capitol Alert (Sacramento, CA)1973-74
    - CARASA News (formerly CARASA Newsletter)1979-82
    - Cassandra1970
    - Catalyst: Chicago Womyn's Paper1980-81
    - Catcall: A Feminist Discussion Paper1981
    - The Catholic Citizen1918-95, [see also St. Joan's International Alliance Bulletin]
    - The Catholic Suffragist1915-18
    - Champion of Humanity1874
    - Changing Woman: The National Networking Publication for Women1985-86
    - The Changing Woman1971-75
    - Channels (National Publicity Council for Health and Welfare Service)1943, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Charity Organization Bulletin (Charity Organization Society of the City of New York)1929-32
    - Chomo Uri: A Woman's Multi-Arts Magazine1974-79
    - Christian Women's Voice1989-90
    - Chrysalis1977-79 [?]
    - The Church Woman1943-79
    - Clearinghouse International Newsletter1976-82
    - The Cleveland Feminist1973-74
    - The Clipper (National Society of New England Women)1961-
    - Clit 0071986
    - The Closet Door1971-72, undated, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - The Clubwoman, [see General Federation News 1897-1904, Neilson Microfilm 425]
    - CLUW News1975-83
    - Coalitions: Women's Liberation Center of Michigan1971
    - Coalition of St. Louis Women1974-75
    - Co-ed1968-71
    - Colorado Woman1980-81
    - Come Out!1969-71
    - Coming Out Rage1973, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Comment1973-86
    - Common Cause, [see Women's Suffrage: The Common Cause of Humanity]
    - Common Lives/ Lesbian Lives1981-94
    - Common Woman - A Vermont Women's Publication of News, Culture, and Dialogue From a Feminist Perspective1979-84
    - Compact, [see Women in Action]
    - Conditions - A Magazine of Writing by Women with an Emphasis on Writing by Lesbians1977-88
    - Congressional Clearinghouse on Women's Rights1975-79
    - Connections: Center for the Study, Education, and Advancement of Women1981-82
    - Connexions1981-95
    - Conscience (Catholics for Free Choice)1982-93
    - Contraceptive Education Bulletin1997-
    - Contraceptive Practice (Great Britain)1938, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Contraception Report1993-
    - The Cooperative Bureau for Women Teachers1925-27
    - Cosmopolitan1953-92
    - Council for Women in Independent Schools Newsletter1975-80
    - Council of Women's Organizations of Israel1959-60
    - Country Crafts (Country Women's Association of Victoria, Australia)1967-69
    - The Country Woman1960-74
    - Country Women1973-79 [?]
    - Countrywoman of Western Australia1966-68
    - Courage: Newsletter of the Loretto Women's Network1987 -2008
    - Courage Berliner Frauenzeitung1976-84
    - Cowrie1973-74
    - C.O.Y.O.T.E Howls1973-79
    - Cover Letter - Older Women's League1980-81
    - The Creative Woman1977-81
    - Chronicle1985
    - CSAC (Chicana Service Action Center, Los Angeles)1973-78
    - Current Literature in Family Planning1972-95
    - Czechoslovak Woman1962-68
  - D
    - Daily Breakthrough1977
    - The Delineator1892-02, 1914-39
    - The Delta1969-70
    - Delta Newsletter1968-70
    - Demorest's Monthly Magazine1883
    - Die Deutsche Kampferin1935
    - Distaff - Dialogue for Southern Women1974-82
    - The District of Columbia Clubwoman1945-48
    - Do It NOW, [see National NOW Times]
    - Donne1938
    - Downtown Women's News (San Francisco)1976-79
    - Les Droits Des Femmes1913-63
    - Dyke1975-78
    - Dyke Doings1976, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Dykes and Gorgons1973
  - E
    - Earth's Daughters1971-
    - Ebony1966
    - Echo of Sappho (New York Area Women)1972, [located in Flat File]
    - Ecos de America - Caracas1951-57
    - Ecos Nacionales (National Conference of Puerto Rican Women)1977
    - Ecstasy (Gay Revolution Party)1972
    - The Education of Women1958-61
    - Effe (Rome)1977-79
    - Eleanor Kirk's Idea1892-93, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
    - Emma (Germany)1977-93
    - Endeavor (Netherlands)1956-69
    - The Englishwoman1909-21
    - The Englishwoman's Review1873-1910
    - Enterprising Women, [see Artemis]
    - Equal Opportunity Forum1979-82
    - Equal Rights1923-82
    - Equal Rights Index1930-49
    - Equal Rights Monitor (formerly ERA Monitor)1975-77
    - Equal Times1975-84
    - Equinox1977-78
    - Essence1970-7
    - Eugenesia (Mexico)1943-45, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Eugenical News (later Eugenics Quarterly)1916-49, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Eugenics1929-31, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Eugenics Quarterly (formerly Eugenical News)1954-67, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Every Other Weekly1970
    - Every Woman1970-72
    - The Executive Woman1973-81
    - Exponent II1975-93
  - F
    - F Magazine (France)1978-82
    - Facts on Women Workers1946-61
    - Facts for Women1943-45
    - The Family Guardian1939-45
    - Family Planning (The Family Planning Association, London)1952-76, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Family Planning News (India)1960-61, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Family Planning News (Japan)1961, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Family Planning Perspectives1969-
    - Family Planning/Population Reporter1972-81, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Family Planning Today (Great Britain)1976-96
    - Family Voice (Concerned Women for American)1991-94
    - Far and Near1890-94, [see microfilm M36]
    - Farm Woman - National Report1979-81
    - Fat!So?1994
    - Fem - Publicacion Feminista (Mexico)1976-89
    - Female Liberation Newsletter (Cambridge, MA)1970-74
    - Female Liberation Newsletter (Minneapolis)1971
    - Femina1914
    - Femina (a Times of India Publication)1976-83
    - A Feminary Newsletter (Chapel Hill, NC)1974-82
    - Feminine Connections (San Francisco)1986
    - Feminist Alliance Against Rape Newsletter, [see Aegis]
    - The Feminist Art Journal1972-77
    - Feminist Broadcast Quarterly1992-94
    - Feminist Collections1987-96
    - The Feminist Connection, (Madison, WI)1981
    - Feminist Communication Collective (Montreal)1973-75
    - Feminist Communications (San Diego)1977-79
    - Feminist Party News1972
    - Feminist Periodicals1987-96
    - Feminist Renaissance1983
    - Feminist Review1979-88
    - Feminist Review (New Women's Times)1978-84
    - Feminist Studies1972-73, [see microfilm M20]
    - The Feminist Voice1971-72
    - Feminist Women's Health Center Report (Los Angeles)1975
    - The Feminist Writers' Guild1985-87
    - Feminists for Bisexual Freedom1975-76
    - Femme (Atlanta)1983
    - La Femme Polonaise1931, [see Countries Collection]
    - Femmes - Marie Claire1978-81
    - Femmes - France1938
    - Des Femmes en Movements Hebdo (France)1981-82
    - Femmes Suisses et le Mouvement Feministe (Switzerland)1981
    - Femsignal1976
    - F.E.W.'s News and Views (Federally Employed Women)1969-82
    - Fifty-one Percent1973-74
    - The Fight for Reproductive Freedom1996-2000
    - Fighting Woman News1975-93
    - Fireweed1979-87
    - Fireworks - The Feminist Journal of John Dewey High School (Brooklyn, NY) 1980-82
    - The First Revolution - a Journal of Female Liberation1971
    - Flash1978-79
    - Focus, a Journal for Gay Women1971-82
    - For Women Only (The Women's Institute, Chicago)1973-74
    - The Forerunner1909-16
    - Forum - National Action Forum for Older Women1978-80
    - The Forum Extra1890
    - Four Lights (Women's International League for Peace and Freedom)1941-70
    - La Francaise - Journal d'Education et d'Action Feminines1927-35
    - Frank Leslie's Lady's Magazine1871-81, [shelved under title Leslie's Lady's Magazine]
    - Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly1876-1905, [shelved under title Leslie's Monthly]
    - Frau und Frieden1952-74
    - Frauen in Amerika1978
    - Freedom Organizing Series (Kitchen Table: Women of Color Press)1985-86
    - The Freewoman1911-12
    - Friend of Virtue1839-46
    - Front Page (Bloomington, IN)1974
    - Frontiers1975-94
    - From the Flames1997
    - The Fujin to Nippon (in Japanese) dates unknown
    - Full Moon, undated 1972?]
    - The Furies1972-73
    - The Future is Female1982
  - G
    - Gay Activist1973, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Gay Community News1973-89
    - Gay Flames (New York City)1971
    - Gay People and Mental Health1973, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Gays on the Hill - Newsletter of Washington DC Universal Fellowship of Metropolitan Community Churches1976
    - La Gazette des Femmes (Quebec)1980-81
    - Gems of Poetry1883
    - General Director's Letter (American Association of University Women)1941-70
    - General Federation News [changed to The Clubwoman] (General Federation of Women's Clubs)1928-57
    - Girls Ink (Girl's Incorporated - New York, NY)1996-
    - Girls' Own1981
    - Girl zines (many titles), [see separate finding aid]
    - Godey's Lady's Book1830-96
    - Gold Flower - A Twin Cities Newspaper for Women1972-1975
    - Good Housekeeping1888-1992
    - Goodbye to All That1970-77
    - Gossip1986, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Graduate Woman1979-88
    - La Grande Reforme1933-39,1947 ,1949, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Guide: The National Women's Political Review (Women's National Republican Club)1938
  - H
    - Hadassah Newsletter1938-99
    - Hag Rag1992-93
    - Hairy Legged Man-Hating Feminist Gazette undated [early 1990s?]
    - Hamdard-I-Sehat (India)1939, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Harrisburg Area Women's News1979-87
    - Health Right (Women's Health Forum)1974-79
    - Hecate - A Women's Interdisciplinary Journal (Australia)1977-82
    - Helicon Nine - A Journal of Women's Arts and Letters1979-81
    - Heliotrope1976-78
    - Hellenia - Voices of Greek Women1948-67
    - Her Say1980-83
    - Hera1975
    - Heresies: A Feminist Publication on Arts and Politics1977-83
    - Her-self - Women's Community Journal (Ann Arbor, MI)1972-77
    - Hertha1917-75
    - Holland-Rantos Monthly Press Clipping News Service1941-47, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Homemakers1978-79
    - The Home Missionary1855-57
    - The Home Monthly1862-63
    - Homecraft1964-68
    - Hot Flash1981-96
    - Hotwire - The Journal of Women's Music and Culture1984-92
    - Hours at Home1866-69
    - The Household1895
    - Housekeeper's Weekly1890-91
    - Houston Breakthrough1977-81
    - Human Fertility (formerly The Journal of Contraception)1935-48, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Human Rights to Women (HRW) Newsletter1971-78
    - Humane Society News1960-65
    - Hurricane Alice - A Feminist Review1984-88
    - Hx for Her: The Totally Biased Politically Incorrect Party Paper for Lesbians1996
    - Hysteria1970-71
  - I
    - IAW e-Newsletter (International Alliance of Women), 2008
    - I Know You Know - Lesbian Views and News1984-85
    - Ikon1983-88
    - Illinois Women's Agenda1977?-81
    - The Illustrated Women's Almanac1973
    - In News Weekly (Boston)1993
    - In the Running1978-82
    - Independent Woman1936-52
    - The Indian's Friend1883-97, [see also microfilm M59 for 1897-1907]
    - The Indian Ladies Magazine1931
    - Indian Medical Journal1952, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Information Service (Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America)1931, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Informationen Fur Die Frau1951-
    - Ingnue1969-73
    - Instraw News (United Nations International Research and Training Institute for the Advancement of Women)1986-93
    - The Institute for the Study of Women in Transition Newsletter1976-77
    - Inter-Action (Feminist Action Alliance)1977
    - Inter-American Commission of Women News Bulletin1960-64
    - Inter Fem1983-84
    - International Archive of Women and Architecture, 2000
    - International Commission on History of Women in Science1982
    - International Council of Women--Bulletin1928-41
    - International Council of Women--Newsletter1961-67
    - International Council of Women--Quarterly Review1958-61
    - International Family Planning Perspectives1990-91
    - International Journal of Sexology1947-55
    - International Planned Parenthood News1952-78
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation News1961-80
    - International Women's Suffrage News (later became Jus Suffragi)1906-13, [see also Jus Suffragi; International Women's News]
    - International Women's News (International Alliance of Women)1906-2008
    - International Women's Tribune, [see The Tribune]
    - The Interpreter1951
    - The Irish Citizen1915
    - Isis International Bulletin1976-82
    - Isis International Women's Journal1985-87
    - Isis International Women's Journal Supplements1984-87
    - It Ain't Me Babe1970-71
  - J
    - The Japan Planned Parenthood Quarterly1950-55, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Japan Through Women1938-55
    - Japanese Women1938-40
    - Japanese Women's Herald in America1938-40
    - Journal of Asian Women1962-72
    - Journal of Contraception, [see Human Fertility]
    - The Journal of Family Welfare (Family Planning Association of India)1955-85,1998, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Journal of Gender Studies
    - Journal of Heredity1946-49, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Journal of Sex Education1949-52, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Journal of Social Hygiene1940-47, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Journal of the National Association for Women Deans, Administrators, and Counselors1968-79
    - Journal of Reprints of Documents Affecting Women1976
    - Journal of Women's History1989-
    - Journey Womyn (Evanston, IL)1979-80
    - Joy of Gay circa mid-1970s
    - Jus Suffragi (formerly International Women's Suffrage News)1913-24, [see also microfilm M29 for 1906-14; International Women's Suffrage News; International Women's News]
    - Justitia1887-88, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
  - K
    - Kalliope - A Journal of Women's Art1979-87
    - Kentucky Woman1980-81
    - Kinesis - "News About Women That's not in the Dailies," 1976-93
    - Kitty Genovese Women's Project1977
    - Know News1971-80
    - Kvinden og Samfundet (Denmark)1912-1932
    - Kvinn, Bulletinen Lesbianism and Ekonomi (Sweden)1981
  - L
    - Labor Pains (Working Women United Institute)1975-76
    - Laberint (Barcelona)1989-99
    - Labyrinth - The Philadelphia Women's Newspaper1984
    - Labyris1978, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - The Ladder - A Lesbian Review1959-72
    - Ladies' Album1850-51
    - Ladies' Companion1838-44
    - The Ladies Companion and Literary Expositor1838-44
    - The Ladies' Garland1837-47
    - Ladies' Home Journal1887-1992
    - The Ladies Repository (Boston)1838-67
    - Ladies Repository (Cincinnati)1842-76
    - The Ladies' World1895-1917
    - Ladies' Wreath1846-55
    - Lady - Unique-Inclination-of-the Night1976-77
    - Lady's Friend1866-70
    - The Lady's Friend1869
    - Lady's Magazine (or Entertaining Companion for the Fair Sex)1784
    - The Lady's Magazine1784
    - Lady's Pearl1840-43
    - The Laws of Life1862, [see also microfilm M13 for 1867]
    - Lazette: Daughters of Bilitis in New Jersey News Journal1973
    - The Leaping Lesbian, undated, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Lesbia Magazine (Quebec?)1991-94
    - Lesbian Activist (New York City)1973
    - The Lesbian Calendar (Northampton, MA)1994-2001
    - Lesbian Connection1974-2005
    - Lesbian Contradiction - A Journal of Irreverent Feminism1983-89
    - Lesbian Ethics1990, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Lesbian Feminist1973-77
    - Lesbian Feminist Flyer (Richmond, VA)1977-88
    - Lesbian Herstory Archives Newsletter1975-2001
    - The Lesbian Inciter (Women's Learning Institute)1982-86
    - Lesbian London1991-92
    - Lesbian News (Los Angeles)1978-92
    - The Lesbian Outlook, circa 1991, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Lesbian Pride Newsletter1997
    - The Lesbian Reader: an Amazon Quarterly Anthology1975, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - The Lesbian Tide1972-80
    - Lesbian Voices1975-81
    - Lesbians Fight Back1972
    - Lesbians Rising1976, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Leviathan1969-70
    - Libera1972-73
    - The Liberal Thinker1890, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
    - The Liberal Review1904-06, [see microfilm M8]
    - Liberation1976
    - Life (special issues)1956,1968,1975-76
    - Life and Labor1911-20
    - Life and Light for Women1888-1908
    - Lilith (Ireland)1973?
    - Lilith (Seattle)1968
    - Lilith - The Jewish Woman's Magazine1976-80,1990
    - The Lily1854-56
    - LIP - A Feminist Arts Journal1977-83
    - Literary Xpress ("A Free Paperzine for Wimmin of Color")1989-92
    - Living1940, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Living the Legacy (NWHP Gazette)1998
    - Long Time Coming1976, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - The Longest Revolution1976-83
    - The Lotus Leaf1961-66
    - The Lowell Offering1841-45; Vol. II, "A Repository of Original Articles,"(1841-42), [see also microfiche M35 for 1840-45]